Tell me how you think I'm wrong When I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think you love Grace or let it cost
Tell me why you look at me Like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know When I give away my trust
Tell me how I'm
Like that made it actually like a little bit gay, like it was really cool at first like don't you talk to me like this
Don't you ever say that and then at the end it was like little stardust like what the fuck was that?
Now this kid's like nice to meet you ma'am
Joseph Joseph are you there? What was clumsy doing back?
No, I banned that person clumsy. Why is that person clumsy in the chat?
Joe are you ma'am? Are you a mod you take a man immediately?
No, I'm not a mod, but even if I was I die to wield my gun
Okay, it's fine
Do whatever you want with you do whatever you want with your mod Joe do whatever you want with it, okay?
Don't defend me. Don't defend me. Don't you're your best friend in the world. You will stick up for clumsy
You know what clumsy did he took a broom in his butt and you're gonna turn on me for him. Okay?
It's okay. I'm used to it. I'm used to it. I know you're trying everyone's gonna turn on me. It's my fault
Clemsis. Oh, he's fine, right? He's fine, right Rachel
Okay, let's see. I have a song on where's song on recent. Where's it not bury at home a second
Hmm. Oh one second
Mean guys, what the fuck? I mean, it's like I tell him and it's so many times
Oh, here's how you're supposed to act my shit. He can't he can't listen to one time. He can't
No, no, no, no not one time that one time. I ask you
Something do something for me. No, you can't do it. You can't think people like for five minutes
Joe this like five minutes really five minutes. No, no, no, no
Oh, no, no forget about psyche psyche is just a piece of shit right forget about psyche, right Joe?
Forget about it. Forget about him. You know, it's just like clumsy
That guy he oh so much more important. He owe that guy don't offend clumsy. Oh, it's okay. Just
Fuckin say what every one of psychs is psyche say what everyone to say to him right, but not not now
No, no, no, no, no not clumsy not clumsy. Oh
Being gang. Oh, no. Oh my god. I'm so scared. I'm scared of being gang. Oh
Broom game. Oh, oh, please. Oh shove it up my ass the more please. I love it
I love it. Oh, that's what that's what he said and you're on his side
Everyone's not everyone else is the wrong side
Right, it's not it's not the right side. It's the wrong side
They don't get it. They don't get it guys. They don't they will he if I can't explain it to them
They don't get it ever right. It's like it's like it's sad. It's like
Because you know if you think if you explained
They would get doesn't get it Joe doesn't get it. He doesn't he doesn't he wants to be out. Oh, oh
Bring that person back bring that person back
No
Well, how about you go fuck yourself and I don't bring the person back. How about I do what I want it?
How about I have the people I like on my show? How about that concept?
Oh, this is a this is free speed. This is my show is not the American country
My show is like a dictatorship. It's run by me. I mean if you guys didn't get that before
You get it now. This is a dictatorship. It's not a pleasant like little friendly show
Oh, everybody come up and just everybody say what they want to say
No, it's my show and it's they have a testing. You know, I'm saying what do they need to say about me if I just
Let's say whatever they want or they're not gonna say shit about me. They're guys are gonna
Start bullying me. I'm picking on me. No, they're not they would who would do that who would be dumb enough
Who would be dumb enough to do that? Oh, I don't know
Everybody here. I mean please if you're if you're not one of those people just raise your hand, but it's like everybody here everybody
Everyone wants to give me shit really everybody every single person I must I must be the worst person in the world
I must be my fault everything guys Capricorn the Capricorn always takes all the blame and I will I'll take all the blame forever
Being part being a Capricorn I'm used to it
Are you guys used to it? No, you're not because no whatever blames you for anything because I'm the scapegoat
It has to be the January person Janet is evil. I'm evil, right? We're just like the devil
We're definitely we're just the devil incarnated, right?
Right guys, right?
So you've been saying I was look at everything every little thing you say I watch don't think I'm watching
Good lord
It's like I
Want to like explain it. It's like it's like okay, so Ariel Ariel was given this gift. She was given legs
Along the world part of the work then you can say anything. I
Made a similar deal. I can't actually tell you the exact
Everything that happens. You're supposed to figure it out
new world
Goddamn humans
Why why and I'm stuck with these humans, right?
Because I fathered them all right
brick and
Being the devil is not a very easy thing to be right is like
Everyone's gonna say oh, there's a devil. You know, you did everything wrong. It was all your fault. You know what God did
God made a devil. He made me right big point some security hole
I'm gonna get my great pictures. This is getting too emotional now, but I'm gonna tell you the truth now because I'm not now
I mean Ursula, she just exploded into like a bunch of ink and like, you know
Tentacles so I can not tell the truth. Okay here. I'm gonna tell the truth now
I'm gonna tell the truth finally. I get to tell the truth. Okay. Oh
I can't be mad at you because it's like being mad at like
Not a baby, but like someone with severe Down syndrome, it's like being mad at that it's like
They don't know the difference. They're like there. They're gonna be smiling no matter what they're gonna be like
Oh, yeah, everything's good. We didn't we know better, but it's like
Okay, the
Tiles still growing up. I don't know I
Try to tell you guys I try to explain it
I have to put it in music and then it's like and there was oh
You're doing AI music. What is this? What is this? What is this trying to explain things to people in like a way?
Emma showing up and trying to put me back at the filing cabinet. I can't shit. I can't go anywhere. Oh, oh, there's Fred
Oh, this is coincidence Fred shows up everywhere. Oh, that is Emma guys. It's like he's obsessed with me. Do you understand that?
It's Emma
There's no Fred going around spying on me. That's all her. Oh
Fred's all of a sudden in my chat just the same night that she's um, you know all of a sudden she's he's sick
Oh, it's just a coincidence. Oh, well, you're you're why are you so important? You're nobody, you know, you're nothing
Why would she even care? She doesn't care. It's just Emma. Emma, you know
She doesn't you know, she doesn't care about anybody all she cares about is like the alimony and the divorce with the devil aka me
It's not easy being the devil guys. I have to keep explaining to you, but we're like actually like everything
Like we're holding up. We're like the Prometheus. We're like the fucking. What's the guy that goes the Atlas?
We're holding up the whole world on our shoulders for you
And then you're like, oh look at the evil devil. There's the evil devil. Look. There's a weird. He's weird
Stay in it. I'm sick of it. I'm gonna go back
Go make fun of sake. He's crashing out. Look. He's just a he's a little cow. He's nobody
He's nothing. He's just someone to make fun of right. That's what you all thought you all thought
I saw it go through your everyone's mind. I mean even my friends that went through their mind
Oh, this is just somebody got here and it's the fuck with
Okay, believe whatever you want guys believe whatever you want
Who is there for you though? Who is there for you was clumsy beam gang there for you, right?
He was there for you when you needed him
Was he there every day? No, no, no, no, I'm not letting anybody up. I'm waiting till I get my song or song put on
I'm gonna wait a second
I'm not crashing out by the way guys. I'm finally telling the fucking truth
Which I can do for like a long time
I could finally do it because enough people fucking piss God off that he was like, okay
Now you can tell him the truth
mean it's like get a clue you guys are infuriating if I didn't love you so much
I might destroy the world I do love you so much
Don't know why
Because you're like you are like another me in a way, but I don't want to believe that either. How could I be like such a dick?
Like I'm really like really the man of dictum being performed on me
Little bit is a little bit
disturbing little bit
Okay, I can't I couldn't say it before but I can say it now
Why are you guys such fucking assholes like really like why do you have to like pick on?
somebody who is like I
Mean by design never meant to piss anybody off like actually this meant to like help people
I mean, but it's like oh, let's pick on this person
You wonder why people get upset with this world
I'm I'm fucking on my way out. I can't I don't reason I'm not leaving is because I do love you
I would be gone, you know, it's like
Get it
I'm gonna bring up the song you're gonna hear I'll play the song it'll explain everything
I don't know if I'll stick around afterward because
Your face is when you're gonna hear this
But it's okay. It's fine. You asked for it. You did ask for it. You said oh, I want to know everything
I want to know I want to treat you of good and evil. I don't want to treat you three of a life
I told you a thousand times don't eat from the tree of good evil eat from the tree of life
No
Why are children so disobedient? I don't understand why do you and not the children? It's you it's not about eight
It's about you because you are the children of God
And you're gonna pick on God. It's like what is the dealio? I mean, I really I really want to know
I'll do it from here. I'll do it from here. Okay. Okay. I
Got it finally
Like
Laying back smiling
Snacking on flames
Flaming hot cheetos
Drowning over pain
Clumsy Emma
Bita and the rest
Left him behind
Thought they knew best
Now he's stuck musing
With a soul full of ache
Looking like art
But his heart's gonna break
Always the nice one
Handsome and true
Didn't deserve what the trolls put him through
But he wasn't their victim
Oh no, not at all
He was their father
Bruises and all
Chat forgive me
I didn't confess
The truth's a bit messy
that you thought you could school
I'm the one who built the stage where you had cruel
And if I didn't love you, I'd tear it all down
But instead, I just waited
Troll me just make it loud your daddy's still smiling and damn he's proud
Psyche's awake in his patriotic blue
Use this tools
Flaming heart heart and these red